const STORE = [
    // one
    {
        question: 'Which continent includes the Jutland and Iberian Peninsulas?',
        options: [
            'Asia',
            'Europe',
            'North America',
            'Australia'
        ],
        answer: 'Europe'
    },
    // two
    {
        question: 'In 1971, the British government ended its protectorate in the Trucial States. These states form what present-day country on the Persian Gulf?',
        options: [
            'The United Arab Emirates',
            'Saudi Arabia',
            'Iraq',
            'Afghanistan'
        ],
        answer: 'The United Arab Emirates'
    },
    // three
    {
        question: 'Sikkim, a region between Nepal and Bhutan, is part of what country?',
        options: [
            'Pakistan',
            'Myanmar',
            'Bangladesh',
            'India'
        ],
        answer: 'India'
    },
    // four
    {
        question: 'The Sea of Azov borders Ukraine and what other country?',
        options: [
            'Russia',
            'Georgia',
            'Moldova',
            'Turkey'
        ],
        answer: 'Russia'
    },
    // five
    {
        question: 'People in the most populous Scandinavian country celebrate a festival of light called St. Lucia Day to mark the start of the Christmas season. Name this country.',
        options: [
            'Denmark',
            'Germany',
            'Sweden',
            'Norway'
        ],
        answer: 'Sweden'
    },
    // six
    {
        question: 'Which capital city, located about 20 miles from the Adriatic Sea, is a major industrial center for Albania?',
        options: [
            'Berat',
            'Moscow',
            'Tirana',
            'Golem'
        ],
        answer: 'Tirana'
    },
    // seven
    {
        question: 'Iqaluit, which means “place of fish,” is the biggest community on the largest island in the Arctic Archipelago. Name this island.',
        options: [
            'Devon Island',
            'Baffin Island',
            'Craig Island',
            'Amund Ringnes Island'
        ],
        answer: 'Baffin Island'
    },
    // eight
    {
        question: 'Hiva Oa, one of the main islands in the Marquesas Islands, belongs to what European country?',
        options: [
            'France',
            'England',
            'Spain',
            'Portugal'
        ],
        answer: 'France'
    },
    // nine
    {
        question: 'Cenotes, or sinkholes, such as those found on the Yucatan Peninsula are associated with what type of sedimentary rock?',
        options: [
            'Rock-basalt',
            'Quartz',
            'Granite',
            'Limestone'
        ],
        answer: 'Limestone'
    },
    // ten
    {
        question: 'Because Earth bulges at the Equator, the point that is farthest from Earth’s center is the summit of a peak in Ecuador. Name this peak.',
        options: [
            'Mt Bona',
            'Denali',
            'Mt Everest',
            'Chimborazo'
        ],
        answer: 'Chimborazo'
    }
]